http://www.artcobell.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Back to top
Privacy Policy
Artcobell (“Artcobell”) takes the protection of our customers' personal information very seriously and we respect your right to privacy. You can generally browse our web site without providing any personal information. There are places where we request a small amount of personal information; and we want to make sure that you understand what that information is used for and how it will be protected. We make every effort to ensure that any data collected is accurate, timely and secure.
Our information request forms, including any information on your personal identity, is intended to help us direct you to the information you are seeking about our products and policies. To accomplish this, information regarding your request may be shared with our dealers or other business partners.
Artcobell does not rent or sell the customer information entered on this site.
We pledge to maintain the confidentiality of your personal identity information, which will be used only to support your customer relationship with Artcobell, its sister companies and business partners.
Generally, the information Artcobell collects helps us to provide you with the latest product information, promotional information and other information that we feel you may find useful. If you have provided personal information, but do not wish to receive further information from Artcobell, you can simply add or respond to our e-mail and tell us that you do not want to receive future communications. You must be 18 years or older to submit any personal information.
Back to top
artcobell_logo
artcobell_logo_dark
Search form
contact
101
Order Status
Artcobell Update on COVID-19
Dealers
Artcobell Update on COVID-19HOMEPRODUCTSAll ProductsCATEGORYNXT MOV®SeatingStudent DesksSoft SeatingTablesTeacher WorkstationsStorage2D/3D SymbolsSOLUTIONSSOLUTIONS FOR LEARNING SPACEMaker SpaceClassroomsMedia CentersLearning HallwaysCafes & CafeteriasBreakout SpacesVIRTUAL CLASSROOMSLEARNING STRATEGIESNEXTGEN SPACESRESOURCESCatalogWarrantyCase StudyColor InspirationShapes + LayoutsMaterials + FinishesCollaborative Conversion SurveyImage DownloadsAll LiteratureABOUTAbout ArtcobellManufacturingFAQsHow to Buy
Enter your keywords
info links right
contact101Order Status
